chordata.info 2006-06-15

# Gecko Tribe, LLC Privacy & Content Policies

---  
  
Gecko Tribe, LLC Policy Page   
  
**Privacy Policy** :   
  
Gecko Tribe, LLC policies are designed to protect your privacy. 

**Personal Information** : There are a few places on our web site where we ask for personal information like names, email addresses, etc. These are our promises regarding this information: 

  * This information will only be used for the purposes stated clearly on the page where the information is collected. 
  * None of this information will ever be disclosed to anyone without your explicit approval. 
  * We will never use any "sneaky" techniques to get your "approval", like some sites which have "approval" checkboxes checked by default. 

**Cookies** : Our web site uses cookies only in ways which do not invade your privacy. The following describes all of the cookies we send from our servers: 

  * _Hit Counters_ : We count hits on many of our pages to help us gauge and improve our web design. To avoid counting the same person twice if they return to a page they have already viewed, we send a cookie when we count a hit, and don't recount the same person when they come back to a page. This cookie contains no personal information, and does not allow us to track how a person is moving through our site. The cookie expires and is deleted from your computer automatically when you quit your web browser. 
  * _Discussion List Login_ : When you log into any of our discussion lists, or add-on story programs, a cookie is sent which contains the user name you selected and a randomly generated number. This is used to ensure that the proper person is credited for each post. The email address you used to register is **not** shown to anyone. You may participate anonymously in any of these forums, in which case no cookies are sent. 
  * _Shopping Cart_ : Our shopping cart system sends a cookie containing only a random string of characters which is used to identify which shopping cart it yours. It contains no personal information whatsoever, and expires and is deleted from your computer automatically when you quit your web browser. 

**Content Policy** :  
  
**Decency** : Gecko Tribe, LLC is committed to providing internet content that is suitable for viewers of any age, and is in line with traditional values. We will never post anything pornographic, graphically violent, supportive of "alternative lifestyles", or otherwise unsuitable for some viewers. 

**Intellectual Property** : Some areas of our web sites allow visitors to post content directly. Any postings which, in our opinion, violate the intellectual property rights of others will be removed. Examples include posts which violate copyright laws, plagerize material, etc.   
  
* * *

© 2001, Gecko Tribe, LLC
